

#### PERSONAL

- Name
- Nada Gomaa
- ♠ Address 8 Makhlouf Nour El-Din Street, Al-Ashreen, Faisal 11865 Cairo
- L. Phone number 01121226254
- M Email anody694@gmail.com
- Date of birth 01-11-2000
- Place of birth Giza
- Gender Female

#### INTERESTS

- Reading books
- Acting
- Math
- learning somethings knew

#### LANGUAGES

Arabic English



# NADA GOMAA

My name is Nada. I'm 22 years old. I worked as a senior receptionist with 3 years of experience in problemsolving and project management and I have good communication skills by which I can convince the customer to buy companies services and offers in addition to that I have communication with different nationalities.



#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Oct 2019 - Aug 2022 Senior receptionist

Cairo

I worked in el shrouk scan and lap responsible for leading 4 Employees. solving Employees problems with system or patients.

I am the assistant of the manager and in the absence of the manager I communicate with Bank transactions Dealing with insurance companies.

Sep 2022 - Jul 2022



## **EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS**

**Bacharel em Direito** Jul 2019 - Jun 2023 om el momenen, Cairo



### **SKILLS**

Communication with computer \* \* \* \* ICDI

Data entry